Guide to the Stanford University, Faculty Senate, Records SC0193
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Committee records, 1949-2011; Accession ARCH_2014_115
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors Part 1, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors Part 1, 2007-2008 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors Part 2, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors Part 2, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors Part 2, 2007-2008 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors, 2006-2007 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Department Report, Anthropology, Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Department Report, Chemistry, Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Department Report, Comparative Literature, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Department Report, Developmental Biology, Undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Department Report, Environmental Engineering, Undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Department Report, Engineering Economic Operation System Research, Undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - FRI Closure, Undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Report, Geological and Environmental Science Department Merger, Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Department Report, Business Research, Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Department Report, Italian Language and Literature, Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Department Report, Management Science and Engineering, Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Department Report,Mollecular and Cell Physiology, Undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Report on Graduate Studies, 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Committee of Undergraduate Studies Minutes, 1969-1971 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Committee of Undergraduate Studies Minutes, 1971-1974 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Committee of Undergraduate Studies Minutes, 1974-1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Committee of Undergraduate Studies Minutes, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors, 2005-2006 (Box 8, Folder 3-12)
  - Report, Health Services Research, 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Report, Health Services Research, 1984-1996 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Report, Health Services Research, 2001-2006 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Report, Ethics and Society, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4-6)
  - Report, Humanities, Undated (Box 9, Folder 7-8)
  - Report, IDM: Humanities and Sciences, Undated (Box 9, Folder 9-10)
  - Report, Human Biology, Undated (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
  - Report, Immunology, Undated (Box 9, Folder 13-15)
  - Report, International Policy Studies, Undated (Box 9, Folder 16-18)
  - Report, Grad Special Programs Vol 1, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1-5)
  - Report, Humanities, Undated (Box 10, Folder 6-8)
  - Masters of Latin American Studies Vol 2, Undated (Box 10, Folder 9-11)
  - Masters of Latin American Studies Vol 1, Undated (Box 10, Folder 12-14)
  - Report Jewish Studies, Undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Report, International Security Studies, Undated (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Committee of Undegraduate Studies Minutes, 1980-1994 (Box 11, Folder 1-5)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Standards and Policies, 2009-2010 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Standards and Policies, 2007-2008 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - C-65 JDP, 1981-2001 (Box 11, Folder 8-9)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Standards and Policies, 2006-2007 (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors, 2009-2010 (Box 11, Folder 12-15)
  - Committee of Undegraduate Studies Minutes, 1969-1980 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Committee of Undegraduate Studies Minutes, 1981-1992 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Standards and Policies, 2006-2008 (Box 12, Folder 2-7)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors, 2008-2009 (Box 12, Folder 8-15)
  - Financial Math, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - East Asian Studies, 1998-2011 (Box 13, Folder 3-5)
  - Cancer Biology, 1984-2011 (Box 13, Folder 6-9)
  - Comparative Studies in Race and Ethnicity, 1996-2005 (Box 13, Folder 10-11)
  - Continuing Studies, 1999-2004 (Box 13, Folder 12-13)
  - Feminist Studies, 1986-2003 (Box 13, Folder 14-15)
  - Epidemiology, 1993-2005 (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
  - Individually Designed Major Earth Sciences, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Individually Designed Major Engineering, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Individually Designed Major, 1997-1999 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Biomedical Informatics, 2004-2011 (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
  - Applied Linguistics, 1999-2003 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Biophysics, 1992-2007 (Box 14, Folder 10-12)
  - Education, 1998-2002 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Environmental Science, Technology, and Policy, 1994-2004 (Box 14, Folder 14-15)
  - AP Transfer Credit Report, 1973-1998 (Box 14, Folder 16-17)
  - Committee of Undergraduate Studies Chronology, 1969-1989 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement, 2001-2002 (Box 14, Folder 19-20)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement, 2000-2001 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 3-5)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies Chronology Minutes, 1980-2001 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement, 1984-2001 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Study on Distribution of Grades, 2004-2007 (Box 15, Folder 8-13)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 15, Folder 14-15)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 15, Folder 16-18)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement, 1997-1998 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement, 1995-1997 (Box 16, Folder 3-7)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies Affirmative Action, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 8-9)
  - Western Association of Schools and Colleges Annual Report, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Report of The Register, 1998-1999 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Committee for Undergraduate Majors, 2004-2005 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Committee for Undergraduate Majors, 2006-2007 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Committee for Undergraduate Majors, 2003-2004 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Report Foreign Languages, 1987-1998 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Report Foreign Languages, 1975-1987 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Chronology Committee on Graduate Studies, 1971-1983 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Chronology Committee on Graduate Studies, 1960-1982 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Chronology Committee on Graduate Studies, 1981-1992 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Chronology Committee on Graduate Studies, 1993-1999 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement Exceptions, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies Special Subcommittees, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors, 2004-2005 (Box 17, Folder 3-8)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies Subcommittee on Minority Recruitment Retention, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies Subcommittee on Minority Recruitment Retention, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Committeee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 11-13)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement, 1991-1994 (Box 17, Folder 14-17)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Education, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Education, 1968-1969 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 18, Folder 3-8)
  - Committee on Undergradaute Standards and Policies, 2004-2005 (Box 18, Folder 9-10)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 2003-2004 (Box 18, Folder 11-14)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 1-2)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 2004-2005 (Box 19, Folder 3-10)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 19, Folder 11-13)
  - Committee for the Review of Undergraduate Majors, 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 14-15)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 1-5)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 6-8)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Standards and Policies, 2002-2003 (Box 20, Folder 9-11)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 20, Folder 12-16)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement Exceptions, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 2-6)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 21, Folder 7-11)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 11-13)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 22, Folder 1-4)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 2009-2010 (Box 22, Folder 5-7)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 8-10)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 2008-2009 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 2007-2008 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 2006-2007 (Box 22, Folder 13-14)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 2006-2007 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1969-1970, 1980-1981 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies Western Culture IV, 1975-1988 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies S-REA, 1987-1991 (Box 23, Folder 5-6)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1987-1991 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement Exceptions, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement Exceptions, 1983-1987 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement Exceptions, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement Exceptions, 1977-1980 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement Exceptions, 1974-1976 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement Exceptions, 1972-1974 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 2005-2006 (Box 24, Folder 1-9)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 10-12)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 13-15)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 25, Folder 1-4)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 5-10)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 25, Folder 11-13)
  - Comparative Studies in Race and Ethnicity, 2009 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Medical Information Sciences (Informatics), 2000 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - International Relations, 1999-2011 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Master of Liberal Arts, 2001-2011 (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
  - Modern Thought and Literature, 1985-2009 (Box 26, Folder 4-7)
  - Mathmatical and Computational Science Program, 1989-2003 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Public Policy, 1984-2008 (Box 26, Folder 9-11)
  - Neurosciences, 1962-2003 (Box 26, Folder 12-15)
  - Russian, East European, Eurasian Studies, 2002-2011 (Box 26, Folder 16-17)
  - Science, Technology, and Society, 1998-2000 (Box 27, Folder 1-2)
  - Science, Technology, and Society, 1986-1989 (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies Subcommittee on Minority Recruitment and Retention, 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 5-6)
  - Science, Technology, and Society IDP Review 2006 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - History, 1952-1962 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies IDP Rules, 1993-1996 (Box 27, Folder 9-10)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 13-16)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies Subcommittee on Minority Recruitment and Retention, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 3-14)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies: Subcommittee on Exceptions to Graduate Policy, 1990s-2010s (Box 29)
  - CIV Survey, 1996; 1 optical disc(s) (cd-r) (Box 29)
  - Website Pix, 2000 Fall; 1 optical disc(s) (cd-r) (Box 29)
- Records from Stanford University Archives 4 Digit Collection., Accession ARCH_2015_071
  - Executive Committee records, Subseries 1
    - Executive Committee Minutes: 1941-1943 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 2181 Duplicate Minutes and Data of Executive Committee - President's File: 1914-1939 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Academic Council - Executive Committee 1933 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 2181 Academic Council - Exec. Comm. 1944-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 2181 Academic Council - Executive Comm. 1960- (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Executive Committee - Hearings on Classified Research, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Executive Committee - Hearings on Selective Service (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Investigation of Dean Lucille A. Allen, 1965 (1 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Investigation of Dean Lucille A. Allen, 1965 (2 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Investigation of Dean Lucille A. Allen, 1965 (3 of 3) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Academic Council records, Subseries 2
    - 2182 Academic Council Minutes: May 4, 1904-May 20, 1910, 1904 May 4-1910 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 2182 Academic Council Documents: 1904-1916 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Minutes of Academic Council, 1905-1915 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Duplicate Minutes and Data of the Academic Council - President's File, 1915-1916 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Duplicate Minutes and Data of the Academic Council - President's File: April 1927- June 1939, 1927 Apr-1939 Jun (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Duplicate Minutes and Data of the Academic Council - President's File: Sept 1939-, 1939-1943 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 2182 Academic Council: October 1943-Nov 1948, 1943 Oct-1948 Nov (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Academic Council: Jan 1949-Sept 29 1950, 1949 Jan-1950 Sept 29 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - 2182 Academic Council Minutes: Jan 1951-Oct 1952 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Academic Council Minutes: 1953-1955 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Academic Council Minutes: 1953-1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Academic Council: 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Academic Council: 1959 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - 2182 Academic Council: 1960-1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Academic Council: 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Academic Council Minutes: 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Academic Council Minutes: 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Academic Council Minutes: 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Academic Council Minutes: 1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Academic Council Minutes: 1973 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Academic Council Minutes: 1975 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Academic Council Committee Reports: 1910-1919 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Academic Council - Classified Contracts, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Academic Council - Selective Service, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Academic Council Reports, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Academic Council - Supporting Docs - Letter from Sterling to Lyndon B. Johnson, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Academic Council, Senate of Charter of the Senate of the Academic Council, as approved April 11, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Academic Council, Senate of Rules of the Senate of the Academic Council, as approved November 13, 1969, 1969 Nov 13 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Academic Council, Senate of Materials re. establishment of Senate (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Academic Council, Senate of Reports, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Academic Council, Senate of Reports, 1970- (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Academic Affairs, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Senate press releases (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - 2180 Academic Council Committee of Ten - Report (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Domestic Partners Benefits - reports, etc. 1991-1992 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - 2180/3 Academic Council; Faculty Self-Discipline 1972 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Committee and Senate Handbook (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Academic Council Press Releases (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Report of the Committee on the Professoriate at Stanford, February 25, 1974, 1974 Feb 25 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Rosters, Subseries 3
    - Rosters (as of March 1, 1970), 1970 Mar 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Rosters (as of March 15, 1971), 1971 Mar 15 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Rosters (as of December 15, 1971), 1971 Dec 15 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Rosters (as of December 1, 1972), 1972 Dec 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Rosters (as of December 1, 1973), 1973 Dec 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Rosters (as of December 1, 1974), 1974 Dec 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Rosters (as of November 14, 1975), 1975 Nov 14 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Rosters (as of November 12, 1976), 1976 Nov 12 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Rosters (as of October 15, 1977), 1977 Oct 15 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Rosters (as of October 20, 1978), 1978 Oct 20 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Rosters (as of October 26, 1979), 1979 Oct 26 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Rosters (as of October 31, 1980), 1980 Oct 31 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Rosters (as of November 2, 1981), 1981 Nov 2 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Rosters (as of October 25, 1982), 1982 Oct 25 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Rosters (as of October 22, 1983), 1983 Oct 22 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Rosters (as of October 20, 1985), 1985 Oct 20 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Rosters (as of October 30, 1986), 1986 Oct 30 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Rosters (as of October 30, 1987), 1987 Oct 30 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Rosters (as of October 21, 1988), 1988 Oct 21 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Rosters (as of October 27, 1989), 1989 Oct 27 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Rosters (as of October 26, 1990), 1990 Oct 26 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Rosters (as of October 18, 1991), 1991 Oct 18 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Rosters (November 18, 1992), 1992 Nov 18 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Rosters (October 11, 1993), 1993 Oct 11 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Rosters (October 1994), 1994 Oct (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Faculty Senate records, 1966-2016; Accession ARCH_2017_095
  Arrangement
  Arranged by Senate document number
  - Supporting materials
    Conditions Governing Access
    - Senate documents #101-280 (Box 22)
    - Senate documents #281-587 (Box 23)
    - Senate documents #588-937 (Box 24)
    - Senate documents #938-1208 (Box 25)
    - Senate documents #1209-1524 (Box 26)
    - Senate documents #1525-1795 (Box 27)
    - Senate documents #1952-2230 (Box 28)
    - Senate documents #2231-2472 (Box 29)
    - Senate documents #2473-2742 (Box 30)
    - Senate documents #2743-2959 (Box 31)
    - Senate documents #2960-3207 (Box 32)
    - Senate documents #3208-3432 (Box 33)
    - Senate documents #3433-3625 (Box 34)
    - Senate documents #3626-3868 (Box 35)
    - Senate documents #3869-4102 (Box 36)
    - Senate documents #4103-4317 (Box 37)
    - Senate documents #4318-4598 (Box 38)
    - Senate documents #4599-4792 (Box 39)
    - Senate documents #4793-4968 (Box 40)
    - Senate documents #4969-5128 (Box 41)
    - Senate documents #5129-5305 (Box 42)
    - Senate documents #5307-5472 (Box 43)
    - Senate documents #5473-5652, 2003-2004 (Box 44)
    - Senate documents #5653-5805, 2004-2006 (Box 45)
    - Senate documents #5806-5969, 2006-2007 (Box 46)
    - Senate documents #5970-6119, 2006-2008 (Box 47)
    - Senate documents #6120-6289, 2008-2010 (Box 48)
    - Senate documents #6290-6459, 2010-2011 (Box 49)
    - Senate documents #6460-6650, 2011-2012 (Box 50)
    - Senate documents #6651-6780, 2012-2013 (Box 51)
    - Senate documents #6780-6897, 2013-2014 (Box 52)
    - Senate documents #6898-7176, 2014-2015 (Box 53)
    - Senate documents #6942-7188, 2015-2016 (Box 54)
  - Executive Committee, 1966-1968 (Box 21)
    - Executive Committee (Box 22)
  - Steering Committee, 1966-2016
    - Steeering Committee documents # 101-198 (Box 3)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 199-795 (Box 4)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 796-1254 (Box 5)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 1255-1661 (Box 6)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 1662-2198 (Box 7)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 2199-2752 (Box 8)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 2753-3434 (Box 9)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 3435-3960 (Box 10)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 3961-4461 (Box 11)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 4962-4943 (Box 12)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 4944-5303 (Box 13)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 5304-5654 (Box 14)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 5655-5965 (Box 15)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 5966-6325 (Box 16)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 6326-6521 (Box 17)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 6522-6937 (Box 18)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 6938-7217 (Box 19)
    - Steeering Committee documents # 7218-7804 (Box 20)
  - Committee on Academic Appraisal and Achievement (C-AAA)
    - 1971-1988 (Box 60)
    - 1988-2003 (Box 59)
  - C-AAA EIT
    - 1978-1998 (Box 60)
    - Annual Reports, -2000 (Box 60)
  - C-ACIS
    - 1983-2010 (Box 59)
  - Committee on Committees (C-OC)
    - 3219-3627 (Box 2)
    - 3628-, 1988-2012 (Box 3)
  - Committee on Graduate Studies (C-GS)
    - -1987 (Box 62)
    - 1987-2007 (Box 61)
    - 2007-2012 (Box 60)
  - Committee on Libraries (C-LIB)
    - 1970-1995 (Box 1)
    - 1995-2013 (Box 2)
    - Annual Reports, 1969-2001 (Box 1)
  - Committee on Research (C-RES)
    - 1966-1999 (Box 55)
    - 1999-2013 (Box 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1969-2000
  - Committee on the Review of Undergraduate Majors (C-RUM)
    - 2002-2013 (Box 56)
  - C-UA FA
    - 1969-2015 (Box 56)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Standards and Policy (C-USP)
    - 2012 (Box 58)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Studies (C-US)
    - 1968-1987 (Box 58)
    - 1987-2003 (Box 57)
    - Annual Reports, 1997-2001 (Box 58)